Today,
Windy.
Wow, Anko!
Ta-da!
In case you are wondering, the stone from the noodle
Yes, so, Mezakuranbo is walking in the middle of the remo meter people stop
That kind of thing
Yes, I came by.
Maybe it's nice, but after walking for about 5 or 10 minutes, there seems to be a place where you can enjoy the atmosphere
I heard that there is a place where you can get a pass and have a good time.
It's a very nice place with a great atmosphere, but it's also very nice in various ways.
I was actually wearing a one-piece dress at the house today, but I had planned to come.
I was going to come, but I had to take this one off.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a place to stay for a long time.
It's a beautiful, long-term bridge with a lot of natural beauty.
I love this view! It's in the mountains, so it's good if you're coming by car or something.
It's in the mountains, so it's good if you're coming by car. Well, let's find some tea cakes!
Sweets... how do you read this?
I'll go look for some snacks.
It's cold.
Maybe some watermelon Daifuku?
It's warm.
Fried manjyu, fried manjyu, fried manjyu!
I hope you're used to buying deep-fried manjus.
Okay, so...
Deep-fried manju
We just got our hands on some fried manju, didn't we?
Freshly fried, right?
Yes, freshly fried.
It's like this, what does the visual say?
The original
It's the original, or rather, it's called “Aged Manju”.
Bon appétit!
Is it famous?
I think it's famous.
It was placed next to the cash register.
I'm going to try it right away.
But even if I don't eat it, I can tell it goes well with tea.
It looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
It's fried so well!
It's filled with a lot of bean jam.
It's so good!
You can see the river right in front of it.
You can see the river right in front of you, and the streets are so Japanese.
It's so stylish.
I think it's great in the summer.
It's almost summer, Sheldon. Tea is good here. I know. I think it's great for summer.
It's pretty close to summer already.
But I think you can enjoy it in different seasons.
The climate is nice in fall or something, and summer is surely another way to enjoy it in summer.
I wonder if the autumn leaves will be beautiful.
Oh, there will be a lot of them.
It's going to be beautiful.
But you should definitely eat this.
Fried manjuu of Ginzan Onsen (Ginzan Hot Springs).
It is very delicious, so please eat it!
It is not too sweet and full of red bean paste!
Delicious!
Sendai was like this, right?
Eggy and cold in the mountains
Really cold!
Really cold.
What's with all the kimonos? Kimono?
Yukata?
There are people sightseeing in yukatas, and they look really nice.
I could tell you to take it with you in private, but...
That book...
It's really delicious.
I don't think I've ever eaten anything so delicious! The cherry blossoms were delicious, of course, but I think the number one thing that goes best with tea is a fried manjuu...
Nico Choo.
Nico-doo!
That's so true!
I've only eaten two.
Wait, the view is great!
I know.
I'm so sorry I'm wearing a fake dress.
I was lying a little too.
But I thought I was wearing layers.
I thought my outfit was too thick.
I was thinking that maybe I'm just a little too hard through it all.
I've never been to Yamagata Prefecture.
You know, there's this bridge.
There are so many of them.
I feel like I'm in Edo.
I didn't know Yamagata was like this.
I didn't know that either.
What's this again?
Wow, kimonos!
I hear that's why everyone goes there.
I see.
Well, a footbath!
All of these are footbaths, they say!
The rain is getting heavier.
Let's take a look.
Want to take a look?
I'd like to take a look.
Are those towels for feet?
I'm sure.
That's a lot of towels.
Look at this.
I was just thinking... the beef tongue salt is changing.
I'm a little curious.
Oh!
Oh, it's like watermelon water, isn't it?
Fashionable!
There are a lot of Japanese style products like this.
I want this, I want this!
I'm so confused.
It's cute, isn't it?
So cute!
I want to come and look around now.
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes.
It's raining.
Mikuchan, stand over there.
It's purple.
Don't you think it looks good on me?
This mannequin is promoting me.
If you're a woman who guesses Miku, please take a sightseeing tour with this cut! Yes, that's right!
Peak my central beauty. The beginning is this floral one.
Pleased to meet you. Here we are.
Taisho Roman lyrics costume
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you Oh, you can go
Hello.
So, I'm going to wear a kimono.
I'm going to wear a kimono.
I'm going to choose one now.
Then I'd like to show you all.
Here we go.
What do you want to do, Miki?
I have purple, so I should probably wear purple.
But why don't you wear what you want to wear?
Surprisingly, I like black.
This one is surprisingly...
But it's a little gaudy.
This one catches my eye the most.
Oh, that's nice.
I already like purple and black.
No, I get it. It's more mature.
But I think this one's good.
It's cute, but it could be this way too.
Yeah, it's okay.
Do you like Natsume or New York?
Natsume. I don't know what to do.
I'm not sure.
I don't usually wear a kimono.
That's right. I don't wear it that often.
I don't wear it that often.
It looks good on you. Flesh.
Do you think it looks good on me?
This one's cute.
I think this one's good, too.
Oh, I think this one's cute.
This one or this one.
Wow, I don't know. I'd like to take a look.
I think it looks good on you.
Do you think it looks good on me?
It looks good on you.
I don't know.
The color is flashy.
Yeah, it's a little gaudy.
This one's cute, too.
Maybe I'll go with purple.
Which do you think would look good on me?
This one's really cute.
It looks good on you.
I think I'll go with this one.
I think I'll go with purple.
Let's stay for the memories.
Did you see any purple ones in black?
I thought so... this... this... this... this...
This one or this one?
This one's cute.
It's hard to choose.
Maybe a darker color would suit you.
What do you think?
Pick one, Miku.
Maybe this one.
This one?
Which one do you want?
Either one.
This way, too.
Which one do you think is better?
I'll go this way.
Excuse me.
Oh!
So, we've got a cute kimono for you to play with.
It's purple and white, with a little bit of purple in the field of vision, and the weather is a little too bad, but they lent us an umbrella and a nice umbrella bag, so I'd like to walk around in this outfit.
I'm going to enjoy myself.
I'm off!
Okay, well, let's go out for a stroll and look for tea vats.
I'm going to eat a variety of delicious foods and look for tea barrels.
We're going to eat some delicious food and look for tea barrels.
Let's go!
What a cute umbrella!
Oh my God, it's a demon!
Look at this!
It's really nice.
One thing I want to say...
I didn't think I'd ever do something like this.
I don't have a lipstick or anything.
I wish I had brought mine, and you both wish you had brought yours.
And you know, before we came to this Ginza Onsen.
We were sleeping like crazy.
So when we arrived, yawning...
I didn't expect to see you wearing a kimono.
I was really surprised.
We came here in such a relaxed manner
I didn't expect it to be like this.
It's too cold
So here we are.
Oh, no.
Here we go.
Oh, no!
Ha-ha-ha.
I can't take it anymore.
It's looking good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
It's like...
Now...
Oh, no, that's not good.
Oh, no.
I just put on some...
I put on some sweet potato udon.
She said she wanted to eat it.
He said he wanted to eat it, and it was almost time to open the lid.
Natsume said she wanted to eat it...
Sweet potato udon? Yay!
Here it is, udon with taro soup!
I want some!
I want some taro udon!
Hey, Murasaki!
Natsume, you look great!
Really?
She's a nice girl.
A good woman? You should copy her.
Let's match our makeup with Natsume's!
Yeah, sure.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It looks like it's going to land in a dark place.
Wow!
Why don't we take a picture together here?
Let's take a picture, let's take a picture, let's take a picture.
Let's take a picture with me.
Thank you.